http://melanomainternational.org/privacy-policy/

Who We AreWho We AreBe On Our PAGEMIF StaffPrograms & ServicesScientific Advisory BoardAdvisory BoardPatrons & SponsorsMIF’s Seal of ApprovalWhat People Say About MIFSun Protective & Awareness ItemsIn MemoryAwareness StoreState Nonprofit DisclosuresMelanoma InfoMelanoma FactsMelanoma PreventionSunscreen SuggestionsExamine Your SkinNewly Diagnosed?Understanding Your PathologyBiopsy: The First StepSentinel Node BiopsyMelanoma Treatment: Stages I & IIMelanoma Treatment: Stage IIIMelanoma Treatment: Stage IVFinding the Right DoctorGlossary of TermsResourcesResourcesGlobal ResourcesCancer CentersOnline ResourcesThe Melanoma BookClinical TrialsDownload a Skin Self-Exam CardDownload a Patient Navigation CardEvents, Webinars & VideosEvents, Webinars & VideosMelanoma Patient VideoEventsHost an EventPast WebinarsUpcoming WebinarsVolunteerBlogBlogMelanoma? The Doctor Is InForum
GO
Login
|
Create Account
Email us for One-on-One Support
Share
Facebook
Twitter
Newsletter
Privacy Policy
The Melanoma International Foundation or MIF is committed to maintaining the privacy of the personal information of visitors to its sites. Our policies are designed to disclose the information collected and how it will be used. This policy applies solely to the information provided while visiting this Web site. The terms of the privacy policy do not govern personal information furnished through any means other than this Web site (such as by telephone or mail).
Email addresses and other personal information
Personal information such as postal and e-mail address may be used internally for maintaining member records,and alerting of additional services available. Phone numbers may also be used by MIF when questions about products or services ordered arise. MIF will not reveal any information about an individual user to third parties except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process.
Cookies
A cookie is a small file stored on the site user’s computer or Web server and is used to aid Web navigation. Session cookies are temporary files created when a user signs in on the Web site or uses the personalized features (such as keeping track of items in the shopping cart). Session cookies are removed when a user logs off or when the browser is closed. Persistent cookies are permanent files and must be deleted manually. The only persistent cookie used on the melanomainternational.org site is created when a user asks to save the user name and password to prevent the need to sign in for each visit. Tracking or other information collected from this persistent cookie or any session cookie is used strictly for the user’s efficient navigation of the site.
Information provided on a form is maintained at MIF for that intended use.
Credit cards
All credit card transactions are conducted over a secure socket layer connection. Credit card information is not stored on the server or re-used in any manner. Only authorized personnel with specific identification and passwords can access credit card information solely for the purpose of performing adjustments or refunds at the customer’s request.
Links
This site may contain links to other sites. MIF is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. The user will know when he is leaving melanomainternational.org because a different browser window will open.
We at the Melanoma International Foundation welcome your feedback. If you have questions or comments about this site, please contact us at contact@melanomainternational.org
UPDATED: September, 2018
Get Email Updates
Subscribe
+ Share our work with peers
Melanoma International Foundation
Our Mission: To develop personalized strategies with patients so they may live longer, better lives.
Our Vision: A future where top-notch melanoma treatment is accessible to all patients globally.
MIF is a 501(c)(3) charity, also registered as a non-profit charity in the state of Pennsylvania, certificate #29498
© 2013 Melanoma International Foundation. All Rights Reserved. Privacy Policy | Terms of Use
Toll-free:
866-463-6663
International:
